<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
	<id>io.gdevelop.ide</id>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<project_license>MIT</project_license>
	<name>GDevelop</name>
	<summary>Fast and Easy Game-Making</summary>
	<description>
		<p>GDevelop is a full-featured, no-code, open-source game development software. You can build games for mobile, desktop and the web. GDevelop is fast and easy to use: the game logic is built up using an intuitive and powerful event-based system.</p>

		<p>With GDevelop, you can make simple projects for fun, create ambitious indie games or even build the next hit, grossing 1 million downloads like some games powered by GDevelop! Professionals, educators or hobbyists all use GDevelop for game making.</p>

		<p>What makes GDevelop unique and so easy to use are the events and behaviors. Events are a powerful way to express the logic of your game, without having to learn a programming language. Behaviors are pre-made logic that you can create and attach to your game objects. It's simpler and faster than code, and super powerful.</p>

		<p>Publish your games on the web, make a mobile app for iOS and Android, publish on Steam, Facebook, Itch.io, Newgrounds, the Windows store... Games created with GDevelop run anywhere and can be packaged in a single click.</p>
	</description>
	<url type="homepage">https://gdevelop.io</url>
	<url type="help">https://wiki.gdevelop.io/</url>
	<url type="bugtracker">https://forum.gdevelop.io/</url>
	<launchable type="desktop-id">io.gdevelop.ide.desktop</launchable>
	<releases>
		<release version="5.0.146" date="2022-10-03">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>Updated to version 5.0.146. See the full changelog in the app.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="5.0.144" date="2022-09-20">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>Updated to version 5.0.144. See the full changelog in the app.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="5.0.143" date="2022-09-19">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>Updated to version 5.0.143. See the full changelog in the app.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="5.0.142" date="2022-09-16">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>Updated to version 5.0.142. See the full changelog in the app.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="5.0.140" date="2022-08-18">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>Updated to version 5.0.140. See the full changelog in the app.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="5.0.139" date="2022-07-22">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>Updated to version 5.0.139. See the full changelog in the app.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="5.0.136" date="2022-06-15">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>Updated to version 5.0.136. See the full changelog in the app.</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="5.0.133-testing1" date="2022-05-02">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>First release as a Flatpak (based on GDevelop 5.0.132).</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
	</releases>
	<developer_name>GDevelop Team</developer_name>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<image type="source">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/4ian/GDevelop/master/newIDE/GDevelop%20screenshot.png</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
